cupsofhope.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy policy | Dannon.com

**Effective Date: April 24, 2013**

The Dannon Company, Inc. ("Dannon"), U.S. manufacturer of DANNON® branded yogurts, dairy snacks, and dairy drinks, provides this privacy policy to describe how we collect and use the information you provide to us through Dannon-controlled websites and digital properties (each a “Dannon Property” and collectively “Dannon Properties”). Please read this policy to understand how we will treat the personal information that you give to us. Your use of any Dannon Property constitutes your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

> **1\. Collection of Information Through Dannon Properties**
> 
> **a. Collection of Personal Information**
> 
> You can visit and browse Dannon Property without providing personal information about yourself. However, your choice not to provide personal information may impact your ability to participate in or use certain features of a Dannon Property. You may choose to voluntarily disclose personal information about yourself. Personal information is your name, postal address, telephone number, and e-mail address. You may provide us with personal information in the following ways: 
>
>> i. **Sweepstakes & Contests.** To participate in an online sweepstakes, we may require you to register and provide us with personal information and certain other information including a username and password. This Privacy Policy applies to sweepstakes we may administer online including through Facebook and Twitter. We will use the information you provide us for purposes including administering the sweepstakes and purposes disclosed at the time of registration. You should carefully review the Official Rules of any sweepstakes or contest in which you participate. You may also choose to review the policies of the social media platforms on which any of our sweepstakes or contests may run, such as Facebook or Twitter, as they may contain additional important and applicable information. 
>> 
>> ii. **Promotional Emails.** Through various Dannon Properties, you can request to receive promotional emails from us. We may also ask if you want to receive such promotional emails from us during a sweepstakes or promotion registration process or other features on a Dannon Property. If you want to receive our promotional emails, you will be asked to provide certain personal information and areas of interest so that we can fulfill your request. If you would like to stop receiving such promotional emails, please refer to the opt-out provisions within the email. 
>> 
>> iii. **Online Communities.** To participate in an online community, we may require you to register and provide us with certain personal information and certain other information including a username and password. We may use the information you provide us for purposes that include monitoring and operating the online community, responding to your specific questions or concerns, and providing you with relevant content and advertising. Please keep in mind that any information you post is available to be viewed by the public. You should exercise caution in determining what information you post. Dannon cannot prevent further disclosure of information from your posts and is not responsible in any way for such use of the information. You should carefully review the Terms of Use of any online community you participate in as they may contain additional important information. 
>> 
>> iv. **Contacting Us.** If you contact us with a question or comment, we may ask for personal information, along with your feedback, so that we can properly address your concern. 
> 
> **Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**
> 
> When you visit a Dannon Property certain information about your visit may be automatically logged, including the Internet Service Provider and IP address through which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site, the pages you access while at our website, and the Internet address of the website, if any, from which you directly accessed our site. We use this information to improve your experience, operate our site, for marketing and advertising, and for other operational purposes. 
> 
> When you visit Dannon Properties, we may set a "cookie" on your browser. A cookie is a small piece of data that is set on your Web browser that allows websites to distinguish between visitors, analyze traffic patterns through our Dannon Properties, and for advertising and other purposes. 
> 
> We also use “pixels,” or transparent images, to help manage online advertising. These pixels are provided by our ad management partner. These files enable us or our partner to recognize a cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. 
> 
> Most Web browser software automatically accepts cookies, but you can change your browser setting to block cookies on your browser. How to turn off all cookies differs for each web browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Mozilla, Chrome, etc.) so you may wish to consult your browser's "Help" menu for additional information. 
> 
> **c. Online Advertising**
> 
> To provide you a more relevant and interesting experience, Dannon may work with third party companies to display ads on the Dannon Properties and elsewhere on the Internet. These companies may use cookies (a small text file), pixels, or similar technologies that are placed in browsers to gather information about your visits to a Dannon Property as well as your visits elsewhere on the Internet. These companies use this information to provide you more relevant advertising known as interest-based advertising. Some of these companies may be participants in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). The DAA offers a choice mechanism with respect to certain types of data collection and use. Visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to exercise choice with respect to participants of the DAA. If you change computers or browsers, use multiple computers or browsers, or delete your cookies, you may need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser. 

> **Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**
> 
> We may use the personal information you provide us for purposes including to respond to your inquires and requests, provide you with information on our products and services and those of third parties that we think may be of interest to you, and for own business purposes. 
> 
> We may share your personal information with third parties for purposes including: 
> 
>   * Help us maintain and operate our website or for other reasons related to the operation of our own business or marketing. 
>   * Ensure any registration process has been properly executed and, if necessary, verify your identity. 
>   * Administer a sweepstake, contest, joint promotion, or other partnership with a third party. 
>   * Contact you with product updates or other promotional notices and information about Dannon and its affiliates. 
>   * Provide relevant online content and advertising. 
>   * Respond to your questions, inquiries, comments and instructions and to retain such requests as part of our consumer affairs database. 
>   * Help prevent fraud or imminent harm and maintain the security and integrity of our systems. 
>   * Monitor online communities. 
>   * Aggregate non-personal information (including demographic) with third parties outside of Dannon for marketing purposes. 
>   * Conduct market research and product development. 
>   * Comply with legal process, including an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise required by law. 
>   * Complete a corporate transaction. As our business develops, we may sell, buy, or transfer corporate assets, and in such transactions customer information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that our website, company, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, personal information may be one of the assets transferred in such acquisition.
> 

> 
> **Other Important Notes Regarding Our Privacy Practices.**
> 
> **a. Children Under Age 13**
> 
> Dannon does not knowingly collect personal information from visitors under the age of 13, except as otherwise set forth below. Most of our Dannon Properties are general audience websites or digital properties directed towards general audiences. For those sites that may be directed at children under 13, we do not knowingly collect personal information without parental consent. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you are a parent concerned that your child may have provided personal information to us, please contact us in manner described in the “Contact Us” section below. 
> 
> From time to time, Dannon may knowingly collect personal information including name, email address, postal address, and a parent or guardian’s email address from children through a Dannon Property. We may use this information for purposes such as the facilitation of children’s promotion, sweepstakes and/or contest. To assist us with the purpose(s) set forth above, we may share this personal information with third parties who are bound by restrictions of use and confidentiality obligations. These third parties may only use this information as mandated by Dannon, and may not make any independent use of this information. 
> 
> As a parent or guardian of a child, you may request to review, and have deleted, any personal information we have collected from your child, and refuse to permit further collection or use by us of your child’s information. You may make such requests by contacting us in any of the ways listed below in the “Contact Us” section. 
> 
> **b. Security**
> 
> We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help secure information. 
> 
> **c. Additional Terms**
> 
> For additional Terms of Use of Dannon Properties, click here. 
> 
> **d. External Links**
> 
> Dannon Properties may contain links to other websites, including those of advertisers. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies provided by other websites before you provide personal information to them. 
> 
> **e. Changes to this Privacy Policy**
> 
> We may change, modify, add or delete portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. We encourage you to visit this privacy policy frequently. 
> 
> **f. Choice/Opt-Out**
> 
> To opt-out of receiving promotional email messages from us, please see the “Choice/Opt-out” section of any e-mail message or see the “Contact Us” section below. We will process your request as soon as commercially feasible. Please note that any request to “opt-out” may still result in us maintaining a copy of your personal information for archival purposes. 
> 
> **g. Contact Us**
> 
> In the event that you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact Dannon in any of the ways noted below. If you are registered user of this website, you may contact Dannon in any of the following ways to request to correct or update your personal information. 

100 Hillside Avenue   
White Plains, NY 10603 

Or call us at1-877-DANNONUS   
Or send an e-mail to [wecare@dannon.com](mailto:wecare@dannon.com)
